One needs the money. One wants the money. Both love the girl.
Stealing Summers is a thriller, drama film directed by David Martín Porras.
Three American expats living in Buenos Aires decide to steal a
large sum of money so they don't have to return home.
But what starts as a game soon turns violent and they find themselves
on the verge of consequences none of them expected.
Alexandra, played by Sophie Auster.
Trevor, played by Wilson Bethel.
Sam, played by James Jagger.
Boyfriend, played by Mariano Martínez.
Stealing Summers is a 2011 American drama film directed by David Martin Porras, written by Matt
Lester, and starring Wilson Bethel, Sophie Auster, James Jagger, and Mariano Martinez.
It was filmed on location in Buenos Aires, and premiered at the 2011 Seminci (also known as Semana
Internacional de Cine de Valladolid or Valladolid International Film Festival) in Valladolid, Spain.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.